Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- "Improving Productivity" - Katzman, Marvin S. "When Robots"., Publication (Box 13)
  - Highlights of New Industrial Relations Literature., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Highlights of New Industrial Relations Literature, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Author: Industrial Relations Center
  - "Institutionalizing and Diffusing Innovations in Industrial Relations"., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Institutionalizing and Diffusing Innovations in Industrial Relations, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Author: Industrial Relations Section
  - "Industrial Relations and Management in Japan: Other Views"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations and Management in Japan: Other Views, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Deindustrialization and the Two-Tiered Society., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Deindustrialization and the Two-Tiered Society, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Author: Industrial Union Department
  - "The Best Man for the Job is a Man"., 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
    January 7 1991
    - Item 1: The Best Man for the Job is a Man, 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Author: Industry Week Survey
  - "How To Avoid Quality Circle Failure in Your Company"., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: How to Avoid Quality Circle Failure in Your Company, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Author: Sud Ingle
  - "Germany's Health Care System"., 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
    February 14 1991
    - Item 1: Germany's Health Care System, 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Author: John K. Iglehart
  - "Germany's Health Care System". Part 2., 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
    June 13 1991
    - Item 1: Germany's Health Care System, 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "Health Care and American Business: One CEO's View"., 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Health Care and American Business: One CEOs View, 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Productivity Today., 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Productivity Today, 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Author: Institute of Industrial Engineers
  - 1985 Productivity Survey: Supplementary Report Exceptional Productivity Improvement Programs., Publication (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: 1985 Productivity Survey: Supplement Report Exceptional Productivity Improvement Programs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ideas to Improve Productivity., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Overcoming Barriers to Productivity: An Agency Call to Action, 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Author: Inter-Agency Barriers Working Group
  - Overcoming Barriers to Productivity: An Agency Call to Action., 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Fifty Years of Cooperation, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Author: International Association of Machinists
  - Fifty Years of Cooperation., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Conditions of Work: Research in Progress, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Author: International Labour Office
  - Conditions of Work: Research in Progress., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Serving American Employers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Author: International Labour Organization
  - Serving American Employers., Publication (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Interest Growing Rapidly in Agencies to Set-up Employee Quality Circles, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - "Interest Growing Rapidly in Agencies to Set-up Employee Quality Circles"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Summary: Government Humanization of Work- A Survey of Seven Countries, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Author: International Institute for Comparative Social Research
  - "Summary: Government 'Humanization' of Work"., 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Knowledge Keeps no Longer than Fish, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Author: Roeland J. in't Veld
  - "Knowledge Keeps no Longer than Fish"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 25)
    June 9 1989
    - Item 1: QC Circles Spur Productivity, Improve Product Quality, 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Author: Robert R. Irving
  - "QC Circles Spur Productivity, Improve Product Quality"., 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 26)
    June 5 1978
    - Item 1: It Started in Germany- And Keeps Growing, 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - "It Started in Germany -- And Keeps Growing"., 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    March 1977
    - Item 1: High Performing Teams: A Definition, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Author: Tom Isgar
  - "High Performing Teams: A Definition"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Employee Ownership and the States: Legislation, Implementation, and Models, 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 28)
      Author: Catherine Ivancic and John Logue
  - Employee Ownership and the States: Legislation, Implementation and Models., 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: A Summary of the Role of Foreman in the Japanese Steel Industry, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - A Summary of the Role of Foreman in the Japanese Steel Industry., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Quality in Practice at IBM, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Author: J.B. Jackson
  - "Quality in Practice at IBM"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: National Workplace Issues Study Shows: Half of Companies who Fire an Employee Regardless of Reason are Sued: Substance Abusers Increasingly Dismissed, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Author: Jackson, Lewis, Schnitzler, and Krupman
  - National Workplace Issues Study Shows: Half of Companies who Fire an Employee Regardless of Reason are Sued: Substance Abusers Increasingly Dismissed., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Team Composition in Organizational Settings: Issues in Managing an Increasingly Diverse Work Force, 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Author: Susan E. Jackson
  - Team Composition in Organizational Settings: Issues in Managing An Increasingly Diverse Work Force., 1991; Publication (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Diversity in the Workplace: Human Resources Initiatives, 1992; Publication (Box 13, Folder 33)
      Author: S.E. Jackson & Associates
  - Diversity in the Work Place: Human Resources Initiatives., 1992; Publication (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Morale Builder: Quality Circles Alone Can't Hike Productivity, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 34)
      Author: Bruce A. Jacobs
  - "'Morale Builder': Quality Circles Alone Can't Hike Productivity"., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 35)
    February 8 1982
    - Item 1: In Society: New Representational Roles for Labor and Management, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 35)
      Author: David Jacobs
  - "In Society: New Representational Roles for Labor and Management"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: The UAW and the Committee for National Health Insurance: The Contours of Social Unionism, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 36)
      Author: David C. Jacobs
  - "The UAW and the Committee for National Health Insurance: The Contours of Social Unionism"., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Enterprise Unions in the United States: A Case Study of Corporate Compensation and Industrial Relations Strategies, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 37)
      Author: Sanford M. Jacoby Anil Verma
  - "Enterprise Unions in the United States: A Case Study of Corporate Compensation and Industrial Relations Strategies"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Environmental Pressure and Union-Management Cooperation: Historical Evidence from the United States 1920-1965, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
      Author: Sanford Jacoby
  - "Environmental Pressure and Union-Management Cooperation: Historical Evidence from the United States, 1920 - 1965"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Union-Management Cooperation: past, present, and future, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 39)
      Author: Sanford M. Jacoby
  - "Union-Management Cooperation: Past, Present and Future"., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Union-Management Cooperation in the United States: Lessons from the 1920s, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - "Union-Management Cooperation in the United States: Lessons from the 1920s"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Postindustrial Manufacturing, 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 41)
      Author: Ranchandran Jaikumar
  - "Postindustrial Manufacturing"., 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 42)
    November - December 1986
    - Item 1: Task Force Encourages Diffusion of Microelectronics in Canada, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 42)
      Author: Harish C. Jain
  - "Task Force Encourages Diffusion of Microelectronics in Canada"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Union, Management and Government Response to Technological Change in Canada, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Union, Management and Government Response to Technological Change in Canada., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: ESOP's White Knights, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 44)
      Author: David L. James
  - "ESOP's White Knights"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 45)
    October 1989
    - Item 1: An Examination of the Team Concept Relationship of General Motors and the UAW, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 45)
      Author: Joanna Irene James
  - "An Examination of the Team Concept Relationship of General Motors and the UAW"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Moving to Autonomous Work Groups at RHM Ingredients, 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 46)
      Author: Phillip James
  - "Moving to Autonomous Work Groups at RHM Ingredients"., 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Commitment at Work: Five Year Report of the Jamestown Area Labor-Management Committee, 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Commitment at Work: Five Year Report of the Jamestown Area Labor-Management Committee., 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Measuring Managerial Layers and Spans, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 48)
      Author: Allen Janger
  - Measuring Managerial Layers and Spans., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Organizing for Flexibility in Financial Services, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 49)
      Author: Allen R. Janger
  - Organizing for Flexibility in Financial Services., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: How to Conduct a Diagnostic Activity Analysis: Five Steps to a More Effective Organization, 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 50)
      Author: Philip Janson Murray E. Bovarnick
  - "How to Conduct A Diagnostic Activity Analysis: Five Steps to a More Effective Organization"., 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Japan: Quality Control and Innovation, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - "Japan: Quality Control and Innovation"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 52)
    July 20 1981
    - Item 1: Japanese Industrial Relations Series: Labor Unions and Labor-Management Relations, 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 52)
      Author: Japan Institute of Labour
  - Japanese Industrial Relations Series: Labor Unions and Labor-Management Relations., 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Joint Labor-Management Consultation System: Its Features and Status, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 53)
      Author: Japan Productivity Center
  - Joint Labor-Management Consultation System: Its Features and Status., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations in Japan- The Present State and Issues, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Labor-Management Relations in Japan--The Present State and Issues., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Productivity Movement in Japan, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Productivity Movement in Japan., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The Productivity Movement in Japan-The Basic Concept of Productivity and the Development of the Productivity Movement, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - The Productivity Movement in Japan--The Basic Concept of Productivity and the Development of the Productivity Movement., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Japan: Myths Behind the Miracle, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - "Japan: Myths behind the Miracle"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 58)
    December 31 1981
    - Item 1: Japanese Management and White Collar Government, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - "Japanese Management and White Collar Government"., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: In Praise of Hierarchy, 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 59)
      Author: Elliot Jaques
  - "In Praise of Hierarchy"., 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 60)
    January - February 1990
    - Item 1: The Strategic Implications of the Factory of the Future, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 60)
      Author: Mariann Jelinek Joel D. Goldhar
  - "The Strategic Implications of the Factory of the Future"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 61)
    Summer 1984
    - Item 1: Employee Participation Program: Prudent or Prohibited, 1992; Publication (Box 13, Folder 61)
      Author: Kenneth A. Jenero Christopher P. Lyons
  - "Employee Participation Program: Prudent of Prohibited?"., 1992; Publication (Box 13, Folder 62)
    Spring 1992
    - Item 1: QWL Current Trends and Directions, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 62)
      Author: David Jenkins
  - QWL--Current Trends and Directions., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 63)
    December 1981
    - Item 1: Work Reform in France: A Ten-Year Record of Continuous Progress, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Work Reform in France: A Ten-Year Record of Continuous Progress., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 64)
    January 1981
    - Item 1: Columbus/American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 64)
      Author: Martin D. Jenkins
  - "The Payoffs of Paying for Knowledge"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: Participative Management: The New Wave, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 65)
      Author: Tom Jenkins
  - "Columbus/American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Quality of Work Life Program"., 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation Initiatives in the Mass Transit Industry, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 66)
      Author: Kenneth M. Jennings Jay A. Smith Earle C. Traynham
  - "Participative Management: The New Wave"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Quality Control through Participation, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 67)
      Author: Susan Jennings
  - "Labor-Management Cooperation Initiatives in the Mass Transit Industry"., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Eclipse of the Public Corporation, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Author: Michael C. Jensen
  - "Quality Control Through Participation"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: A Process Analysis of Labor Management Committee Problem Solving, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 69)
      Author: Todd Jick Robert McKersie Leonard Greenhalgh
  - "Eclipse of the Public Corporation"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 70)
    September - October 1989
    - Item 1: Attitudes and Obstacles Concerning Work Related Learning: A Survey of Missouri Workers, 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - "A Process Analysis of Labor-Management Committee Problem Solving"., 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 71)
    December 28 - 30 1982
    - Item 1: Education and Training in the Missouri Economy, 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Attitudes and Obstacles Concerning Work-Related Learning: A Survey of Missouri Workers., 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: VAG: A Need for Education, 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 72)
      Author: Janette Eadon Johannesen
  - Education and Training in the Missouri Economy., 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: Social Psychological and Neuroendocrine Stress Reactions in Highly Mechanized Work, 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 73)
      Author: G. Johansson G. Aronsson B.O. Lindstrom
  - "VAG: A Need For Education"., 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Stress Reactions in Computerized Administrative Work, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 74)
      Author: Gunn Johansson Gunnar Aronsson
  - "Social Psychological and Neuroendocrine Stress Reactions in Highly Mechanized Work"., 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: The Mondragon System of Worker Production Cooperatives, 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 75)
      Author: Ana Gutierrez Johnson William F. Whyte
  - Stress Reactions in Computerized Administration Work., 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Municipal Employee Assistance Programs: Managing Troubled Employees, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 76)
      Author: Arthur T. Johnson
  - "The Mondragon System of Worker Production Cooperatives"., 1977; Publication (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: Shaping Our Economic Future: Dignity in the Workplace, 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 77)
      Author: Elmer W. Johnson
  - "Municipal Employee Assistance Programs: Managing Troubled Employees"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 78)
    May - June 1985
    - Item 1: His Employees Are the Bosses, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 78)
      Author: Greg Johnson
  - "Shaping our Economic Future: Dignity in the Workplace"., 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 79)
    March 1 1986
    - Item 1: Sold on ESOP's, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - "His Employees are the 'Bosses'"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 80)
    August 8 1983
    - Item 1: Made in America, 1974; Publication (Box 13, Folder 80)
      Author: Richard Tanner Johnson William G. Ouchi
  - "Sold on ESOP's"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 81)
    December 10 1984
    - Item 1: The Role of the Company: The Displacement Problem; Five Responses, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 81)
      Author: Stephen M. Johnson
  - "Made in America (Under Japanese Management)"., 1974; Publication (Box 13, Folder 82)
    September - October 1974
    - Item 1: Quality of Working Life: The Idea and its Application, 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 82)
      Author: Carl P. Johnston Mark Alexander Jacquelin Rubin
  - "The Role of the Company: The Displacement Problem; Five Reponses"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: RINGI: Decision-Making Japanese Style, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 83)
      Author: Jean Johnston
  - Quality of Working Life: The Idea and Its Application., 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 84)
    September 1978
    - Item 1: Total Quality Leadership vs. Management by Control, 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 84)
      Author: Brian L. Joiner Peter R. Scholtes
  - "RINGI: Decision-Making Japanese Style"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Making the Z Concept Work, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 85)
      Author: Charles W. Joiner Jr.
  - Total Quality Leadership vs. Management by Control., 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Theory Z in Practice: One Manager's Story of How He Made the Z Concept Work, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - "Making the 'Z' Concept Work"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Statement of General Motors Corporation on The Changing Work Environment, 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - "Theory Z In Practice: One Manager's Story of How He Made the Z Concept Work"., 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: A Joint Labor Management Communication on Health Care Cost Management, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - "Statement of General Motors Corporation on the Changing Work Environment"., 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 89)
    June 28 1978
    - Item 1: Putting a Lid on Health Care Costs in the Retail Food Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - A Joint Labor Management Communication on Health Care Cost Management., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: Joint Participation Efforts: Risks Differ for Labor and Management, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Putting a Lid on Health Care Costs in the Retail Food Industry., Publication (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Joint Programs Increase Opportunities for Member Participation in Industry Affairs, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - "Joint Participation Efforts: Risks Differ for Labor and Management"., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Item 1: The Productivity Effects of Worker Directors and Financial Participation by Employees in the Firm: The Case of British Retail Cooperatives, 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 92)
      Author: Derek C. Jones
  - "Joint Programs Increase Opportunities for Member Participation in Industry Affairs"., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: U.S. Producer Cooperatives: The Record to Date, 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 93)
      Author: Derek Jones
  - "The Productivity Effects of Worker Directors and Financial Participation by Employees in the Firm: The Case of British Retail Cooperatives"., 1987; Publication (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: British Evidence on the Employment Effects of Profit Sharing, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 94)
      Author: Derek C. Jones Jeffrey Pliskin
  - "US Producer Cooperatives: The Record to Date"., 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Item 1: Inter-Industry Strike Frequencies: Some Pooled Cross-Sectional Evidence from Canadian Secondary Manufacturing, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 95)
      Author: J.C.H. Jones W.D. Walsh
  - "British Evidence on the Employment Effects of Profit Sharing"., 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Item 1: Worker Interdependence and Output: The Hawthorne Studies Reevaluated, 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 96)
      Author: Stephen R.G. Jones
  - Inter-Industry Strike Frequencies: Some Pooled Cross-Sectional Evidence from Canadian Secondary Manufacturing., 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: Volvo: A Report on the Workshop on Production Technology and Quality of Working Life, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 97)
      Author: Berth Jonsson Alden G. Lank
  - "Worker Interdependence and Output: The Hawthorne Studies Reevaluated"., 1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Item 1: Codetermination International Labour Organization Symposium on Workers' Participation, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 98)
      Author: John T. Joyce
  - "Volvo: A Report on the Workshop on Production Technology and Quality of Working Life"., 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 99)
    Winter 1985
    - Item 1: Performance Incentives Work: The Navy's Performance Contingent Reward System, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 99)
      Author: Robert Joyce
  - "Codetermination". International Labor Organization Symposium on Workers' Participation., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 100)
    May 5 - 8 1981
    - Item 1: The Pros and Cons of Participative Management, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 100)
      Author: W. Matthew Juechter
  - Performance Incentives Work: The Navy's Performance Contingent Reward System., 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Item 1: We Are Driven, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 101)
      Author: John Junkerman